I'm getting used to it.
这身体也已经适应得差不多了
From today,
从今天起
HXEROS will be dissolved.
HXEROS即将解散
Welcome back.
欢迎回来
Tya Tya，We come back.
茶茶 我们回来了
What's wrong with your hair?
妳的头发是怎么了
You didn't come back until morning. Are you very mature enough?
玩到早上才回来 你们很「成熟」喔
W... What? until today morning?
玩 玩到早上
It's not like what you think...
不是妳想的那样…
We will go to Anno home together tonight.
今天晚上大家要一起去庵野那里
What happened?
有什么事吗
It's a secret.
这是秘密
Oh! Uncle did not answer the phone.
对了 叔叔他都没有接电话
Do you know what's wrong with him?
妳知道他怎么了吗
I just know that he went out to pick up Jiji. I don't know what happened after that.
他出门接姬姬她们回来后 再来我就不知道了
OK.
这样啊
We'll call him when we are going to go.
等要过去时再和他连络吧
Okay!
也对
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Episode 11 "Goodbye HXEROS"
第十一话「再见了 HXEROS 」
Not a big deal.
不是什么大不了的对手
Are you okay?
没事吧
It's just finished.
我这边才刚结束
Come on, Enjo Retto. Get away from that guy.
烈人 快点离开那家伙
Well, too pity.
很遗憾
You treat it too lightly, guy.
你太掉以轻心了 人类
What happened just now?
刚才那是怎么回事
Enjo Retto, are you ok?
烈人 你的身体不要紧吧
A piece of cake. I just got poked. It's okay.
只是被戳了一下 没什么感觉
What is the exact ability of that Kisei Chuu?
那只规制虫的能力到底是什么
It's...
这个嘛…
Uh!
奇怪
There seems to be a strange feeling in my lower body.
下半身好像有种奇怪的感觉
The Kisei Chuu just now is called the feminization bug.
刚才的规制虫叫女体化虫
It separates the masculine features of the stabbed males.
牠会让被刺到的雄性的男性特征分离
And gradually feminize you, which is terrilble.
渐渐使对方雌性化 是个很可怕的家伙
That is,
也就是说
the weasel-like thing that just ran away was...
刚才跑掉的那只像白鼬的东西…
the male root of Enjo Retto
是烈人的男性根源
It's really gone.
真的不见了
My male roots are gone.
我的男性根源消失了
If you don't get it back quickly to put it back in place
如果不快点抓住牠并放回原本的位置
It will never get back.
就再也无法复原了喔
What? Are you kidding me?
真的假的啊
After I officially take over governor,
在我正式就任知事后
I will change the existing regulations in accordance with the election convention
我将依照选举公约更改现有条例
to reduce the tax loss
减少税金的浪费
doing my best to build a healthy society
为打造出一个健全的社会尽一己之力
It should have escaped from here.
牠应该是朝这边逃跑了才对
Thanks everyone.
非常谢谢各位
What's wrong with you, Tya Tya?
妳怎么了 茶茶
It's ok.
没什么
Well, where did it go?
话说回来 牠跑到哪里去了
That way! Over there.
在这个方向
Oh.
好
We finally caught it.
总算把牠抓住了
What are you doing, so slowly?
你还在慢吞吞的做什么
We'll be late, if we don't put it back soon.
再不快点放回去真的要不及了喔
But, how to do it?
可是要怎么做
Hold it and touch the original part.
抓着牠触碰原本的部位
My body?
这是我的身体？
It really feels more feminine than before.
感觉确实是变得比刚才还要有女人味
Do you want me to help?
不然要我来帮忙吗
No, Thanks.
不用了啦
I am back.
我回来了
Damn!
可恶
Freeze!
站住
Where's my "root"?
我的根源跑到哪里去了
You must have mistaken me. I just...
妳误会了 我这是…
Excuse me, who are you?
请问 妳是哪位呢
Shirayuki didn't recognize me?
难道说白雪没有认出我吗
Well... I'm Enjo Retto's sister, Crimson.
那个…我是烈人的妹妹绯色
I have something to talk with my brother.
我有点事想来找大哥商量
That's it.
原来如此
I'm going to get some tea. Please come in.
我现在去泡茶 请进来坐坐吧
OK.
好的
What happened, Miss Crimson?
怎么了吗 绯色小姐
You doesn't seem well.
妳的脸色好像…
This feeling. Could it be that...
这种感觉 难道说…
I should go to the toilets.
我去上一下洗手间
OK. Rumba, stay there.
好了 伦巴 乖乖别乱动喔
Look at this, Kirara.
妳看好啰 云母
You should do like this when you bathe Rumba.
帮伦巴洗澡时要像这个样子
You don't have to use too much bubbles.
泡泡不会用太多了吗
Rumba easily gets itself dirty.
伦巴动不动就弄得浑身脏兮兮
This's just all right.
这样子刚刚好而已啦
Right? Rumba.
对吧 伦巴
WHO?
谁啊！？
Who's that next to him?
旁边这只又是谁啊
The warm feeling...
这股暖暖的感觉
A bad feeling comes to me.
我有种不好的预感
Hey, who are you?
那个…妳哪位？
This is Miss Crimson, Enjo's sister
这位是炎城同学的妹妹绯色小姐
She seems to be the pet's owner.
似乎是那只宠物的饲主
Are you Miss Crimson?
妳是绯色？
I haven't seen you for a while. You seem to have grown a lot stronger.
一阵子不见 妳好像变壮不少了呢
Really?
是这样吗
Oh no... Hoshino knows that guy.
惨了 星乃认识那个家伙啊
Rumba, it's too dangerous.
这样很危险喔 伦巴
Ouch...
好痛…
Kirara, how did you suddenly slip down?
妳怎么突然滑倒啊 云母
If you have any grievance, turn to Rumba to complain.
有意见就去找伦巴抱怨吧
I think I might as well take a shower.
我看干脆顺便洗个澡算了
Okay.
也对
Will you like to wash together, sister?
妹妹要不要也一起洗
Your clothes are all wet.
妳的衣服都湿透了吧
Come on. Forget it.
我就算了吧
Alright, alright, you don't need to do that.
好了好了 用不着这么客气
Besides,
而且
I also want to know about the weakness of Enjo Retto.
我也想打听一下烈人的弱点呀
I never thought Taoyuan, this guy would be so strong.
想不到桃园这家伙力气这么大
How old are you, Crimson?
绯色今年几岁了啊
Fifteen.
十五岁
Isn't that as same age as Sora?
那不是和宙一样大吗
But I didn't know that Enjo Retto has a sister.
不过没想到烈人竟然有妹妹啊
I used to play with her, too.
我以前也常和她玩在一起呢
So...
所以呢
Crimson, have you falled in love?
绯色妳现在有没有心上人呀
Not yet.
没有啦
Unbelievable!
真可疑
Your breasts grow bigger than mine. Very plump!
胸部长得比我还大 真嚣张
Does your elder brother have someone he likes now?
那妳哥哥现在有喜欢的人吗
I don't mean anything special.
我没有什么特别的意思喔
Momoka just said she wanted to ask your brother's weaknesses,
是因为百花刚才说想问出他的弱点
so I...
所以我才…
I'm not sure what the guy is thinking.
我不太清楚那家伙到底在想什么
But I'm sure that
但有件事我能断言
Whether it was before and now
不管是以前和现在
He remains the same as pure as he's in elementary school.
他的脑袋都还是和小学一样没有改变过
Your little sister speaks well.
妳这做妹妹的讲起话来挺有模有样的嘛
What does the weasel doing?
那只白鼬在干嘛啊
I don't know.
不晓得
Do you also want us to help washing it?
是不是也希望我们帮牠洗啊
Ok, I will help you.
好吧 那我来帮你洗个澡吧
What's that...
那只是…
How about it? Comfortable?
怎么样呀 这里舒服吗
It seems too nice.
牠看起来好舒服的样子
It's like my "root".
简直就像我的男性根源
being cleaned by those two.
被那两个人一起清洗似的
I'm going out first.
我要先出去了
What's the matter, Crimson?
妳怎么了 绯色
Nothing with that weasel?
那只白鼬没事吧
Enjo Retto...
烈 烈人
What the hell is going on here?
这到底是怎么搞的
What we just talked
那也就是说刚才讲的话
had been heard by him?
全被那家伙听见了吗
They're here again.
他们又来了
Broadcast the next news for you.
为您播报下一则新闻
With the inauguration of the new governor,
随着新县知事的就任
The first arrested person has been made as a result of the new legislation.
已出现第一位因为新制定的条例 而遭逮捕的人士
Come here everyone,
大家快过来
The suspect is arrested for committing the crime of compulsory underage indecent assault.
因犯下未成年强制公然猥亵罪 而遭到逮捕的嫌疑犯
It is said to be an employee of the Saitama City Hall.
据传是埼玉市役所的职员
It's part of an unidentified department called the Earth Defense Force.
隶属于一个名叫地球防卫队的不明部门
Is it really?
这不是真的吧
I can't believe uncle will be arrested.
叔叔竟然会被抓
No problem, Enjo Retto.
没问题的 烈人
Anyway, he's your uncle.
毕竟那是叔叔
There must be some mistakes.
这一定是有什么误会
But it has been reported that he's a criminal suspect.
可是都说是嫌疑犯了
Sora
小宙
Enjo Retto
烈人
Anno gave me this.
这是庵野给我的
He said he'll leave it to you, if anything happens.
他说万一有什么事就交给你
Then you can wear the HXEROS battle suit.
这样一来就可以穿着HXEROS战斗服了
HXEROS battle suit?
HXEROS战斗服？
Spinning GEAR's pointer first.
你先旋转GEAR的指针看看
This...
这是…
This is the time when you go out to have fun with Enjo Retto.
这是烈人你们出去玩的期间
Anno made the suit out of my fur/hair.
庵野用我的毛做的战斗服
Try it on. What's the function of the suit?
那到底有什么样的效果
It can increase H-energe and it has H-energe resistance.
可以增幅H能源 还拥有H能源抗性
That is to say...
那也就是说…
That won't get torn again.
这样一来衣服就不会再破掉了
Thank you very much.
真是太感激了
Although the funds will be allocated to us, it is still very troublesome.
虽然上头会拨经费 但还是很麻烦呢
Yes, you're right.
没错没错
And even if you find the suitable underwear as expected,
而且就算找到中意的内衣
It'll break all at once.
也会一下子就破掉
Really poor cost performance.
性价比真的很差
Could it be that...
难道说
uncle did it for...
叔叔他是为了做这些才会…
Enjo
炎城
Yes
是
Yes... I know.
是…我明白了
Is it the call from the head office?
是本部的人打来的吗
What did they say?
他们说什么
The people in the department said they don't know the details either.
本部的人说他们也不太清楚详情
Besides, they said...
而且他们还说
We are in dangerous right now.
我们现在正处于非常危险的状况
What does it mean?
这是什么意思
I don't know.
我不晓得
But
但是
The dorm may be closed because of this matter.
因为这宿舍有可能会被关闭
They want us to take XERO GEAR home right now.
他们要我们带着XERO GEAR立刻返家
That is...
那也就是说…
HXEROS…
HXEROS…
HXEROS's being disbanded for now.
要暂时解散了
Feminization Worm.
女体化虫
Would you want me to turn your "roots" into weasels?
要不要我把你们的根源也变成白鼬呢
A week later.
一周后
Brother.
哥哥
So you're living at home now, huh?
说起来你现在回家里住了喔
But I didn't expect that.
不过没想到
You are barred from entering the dorm.
你竟然会被禁止进入宿舍
You're not going to watch girls take a bath?
你不会是跑去偷窥女生洗澡吧
What? That's not funny.
什么嘛 真没意思
You'd better go and take a shower.
你快点去洗澡吧
I'm still not feeling it.
我到现在都还是没有真实感
It unexpected that uncle's...
没想到叔叔的…
I can't believe our HXEROS will be disbanded.
我们的HXEROS竟然会被解散
You're almost late, but you're really taking your time.
都快迟到了还用走的 你还真是悠哉呢
You don't have the decency to talk about me.
妳也没有资格说我吧
After all, these happened a while ago.
毕竟前阵子才发生那些事
That's why I'm getting less motivated.
所以现在变得有点没干劲
But on the other hand,
不过反过来说
we finally don't have to help with those kinds of heroic activities.
我们终于不必协助进行那种英雄活动了
Just think optimistically.
你就想得乐观一点吧
However...
可是…
None of us participated in club activities.
而且我们也都没参加社团活动
We should enjoy our high school life.
应该要好好享受高中生活才行啊
What do you mean?
这话是什么意思
So
所以说呢
Let me take care of this first.
这个先交给我保管吧
As long as Enjo can enjoy his nice high school life.
只要炎城能好好地认真享受高中生活
I will return it to you.
就还给你
Fireworks convention?
烟火大会？
It's about Fireworks convention time already.
原来已经到这个时期了啊
I want to talk with you about something.
所以我有件事想找妳商量
Oh, I see.
原来如此
You want to invite Enjo's friends to attend the fireworks convention?
妳想邀炎城的朋友参加烟火大会
So you want me to invite Enjo, so he can bring his friends together?
所以希望我邀请炎城参加 好让他带他的朋友一起去吗
But surprise that
不过真没想到
Yang Xiang develops interest for Date.
阳香竟然会看上伊达啊
So what?
又不会怎么样
Kirara and Enjo are still very close these days.
云母最近还不是和炎城很要好
See, you are so well-tied, I just...
看妳们关系这么好我就…
I don't know what to do with you.
真拿妳没办法
You owe me a favor.
妳欠我一份人情喔
Thanks, Kirara.
谢谢妳 云母
Yes, that's it.
没错没错 就是这样
This moment has finally arrived.
这一刻终于到来了
Without HXEROS, there is no Kisei Chuu , and there is no H-energe.
没有HXEROS 也没有规制虫 更没有H能源
And all that high school stuff didn't make sense.
和那一切都无缘的高中生活
That's just the way it is.
事情就是这样
Please save me the weekend schedule first.
先帮我把周末的行程空下来吧
Hey, Hoshino.
那个啊 星乃
Are you inviting me reluctantly？
妳是不是在勉强自己邀请我
I'm not trying to force myself to do that.
我才没在勉强自己呢
So do you want to attend or not?
所以你到底是想去还是不想去
I want to...
我想去…
You're too slow, Kirara.
妳太慢了 云母
Sorry, too sorry.
抱歉抱歉
Thank you all for waiting.
大家久等了
Kirara you also come in a yukata, too.
云母也是穿浴衣过来啊
Date, where's Enjo?
伊达同学 炎城呢
That boy?
那家伙啊
He just said that he was needed by his part-time job.
他刚才说打工的地方找他
So he'll be here later.
所以会晚一点到
A part-time job?
打工？
Special Apricot Candy
特制杏子糖
Thank you for your coming. Please pick one.
谢谢惠顾 请来抽一个吧
Give it to me.
交给我吧
A pity for there's one only.
真可惜 只有一根
Oh... you are so unlucky.
真是的 你的运气太差了吧
Why did you pick without permission?
为什么要擅自抽啦
I think I will success.
我以为会成功嘛
Kirara
云母
Do they have something?
那两人是不是有什么啊
Who knows?
谁知道呢
May be somewhere we don't know
可能是在我们不晓得的地方
something happened
发生过什么事吧
Interesting that
不过没想到
The two people who are arguing every day are so intimate.
天天在斗嘴的那两个人竟然会这么要好
Don't talk about others.
还说别人呢
You've suddenly become very close to Enjo.
妳还不是突然和炎城的感情变得很好
Because we were childhood friends.
因为我们是儿时玩伴啊
But then again...
话又说回来
It's a good chance to come to see fireworks display.
难得过来参加烟火大会
What the hell is that guy doing?
那家伙到底在搞什么啊
I'm gonna go to the toilet.
我去上一下洗手间
Sorry to be late.
抱歉来晚了
I just arrived here too.
我也才刚到而已
I mistook the masked man for Kisei Chuu for a second.
我刚才一瞬间把那个戴面具的人错看成规制虫了
It's an occupational hazard, isn't it?
这根本已经是职业病了吧
So many people.
好多人
There's nothing we can do.
没办法了
God, forgive me.
神啊 请原谅我
Enjo
炎城
Hoshino
星乃
Are you OK?
你没事吧
Why are you still here?
而且你怎么会在这里
I encountered Kisei Chuu on my way here.
我在过来的路上遇见规制虫
As expected, I wanted to defeat her, but this is what happened.
原本想打倒她 结果就变成这样了
Oh no.
真是的
Can't you behave yourself at a rare fireworks event?
难得的烟火大会你就不能安份一点吗
What?
什么嘛
I'm still looking forward to it.
亏我还这么期待
Sorry.
抱歉抱歉
It's my fault for forgetting that there is no XERO GEAR.
都怪我忘记没有XERO GEAR
And still trying to battle with her.
还想要去阻止对方
Sorry. It's my fault.
对不起 这都是我的错吧
Don't worry about it.
没有这种事
Since today's a fireworks show, there's lots of people.
不过因为今天是烟火大会 聚集了很多人潮
Kisei Chuu won't miss this opportunity, right?
规制虫不可能会放过这种机会吧
Hoshino
星乃
Do you know where the fireworks are set?
你知道施放烟火的地点在哪里吗
I think it would be there.
我想应该是在那个方向
Really?
是吗
Wait. What's going on?
等等 到底是怎么回事
That guy!
那家伙
Come to attack here.
是来袭击这里的
It's OK with them.
他们没事
They just faint for H-energy was sucked away.
只是H能源被吸走昏倒了而已
Enjo, look!
炎城 你看
According to the previous information we heard before,
根据之前听说的情报
it's just launching this kind of gunpowder into the sky.
不过就只是将这种火药弹朝天空发射
I don't know how it comes true that human beings in pairs.
不知为何就会让人类变得成双成对
Please, stop!
拜托妳快住手
Many people have been looking forward to this day.
有很多人一直在期待着这一天的到来啊
Stupid humans go with the flow of time and emotion.
顺着一时间的情感 随波逐流的愚蠢人类
Like this creature,
像这样的生物
it's better to explode with the gunpowder.
还是和火药一起爆炸算了
So now,
所以我现在
I will shoot all the gunpowder here at the place where the humans gather.
要将这里所有的火药 射向那个人类们聚集的地点
NO, wait.
等一下
We have to do something.
得快想想办法才行
You'll be turned against us again if you go there.
你直接过去又会被反将一军的
And we've got a ban on heroic activities from head office.
而且本部已经下达英雄活动的禁止令了
I haven't mentioned it to Hoshino.
我还没向星乃提起过吧
Why did I start to blot out Kisei Chuu?
我为什么会开始歼灭规制虫的活动
For the beginning
我一开始
It's because Kisei Chuu leave you traumatized.
是因为无法原谅让妳留下心理创伤的规制虫
That's why I listened to my uncle's instructions.
所以我才会听叔叔的指示
To help with HXEROS activities.
协助进行HXEROS的活动
Enjo
炎城
When I were HXEROS,
但是我在当HXEROS的过程中
I've learned one thing.
明白了一件事
What we're guarding
我们在守护的
is people's love that matters.
其实是人们的恋情才对
If you can't protect others' love,
无法守护他人恋情的家伙
how can you protect your love?
又要怎么守护自己的恋情
Come out, Black Kirara.
出来吧 黑云母
What happened?
怎么了
I'm surprised you invite me out on your own.
妳竟然会主动找我出来 真稀奇
Whatever, I want to ask you to store the H-energy now.
我现在不论如何都想拜托妳储存H能源
A piece of cake.
这只是小事一桩而已
Lend me your body first.
先把身体借我一下吧
Enjo Retto, come here.
小烈 你先转过来一下
That? what's...
那个 这是…那个…
Hoshino...
星 星乃
First, I will...
首先我要…
Beat that guy.
打倒这家伙
Ready to go.
开始了
Fabulous!
好棒喔
It would be nice if Kirara also watches this elsewhere.
要是云母也在其他地方看就好了
Do not stare at me always.
不要一直盯着我看啦
I will be embarrassed.
这样我会很难为情的
Sorry.
抱歉
I want to return it to you. Fortunately, so I brought it here today.
我想把它还给你 幸好今天有带过来
So everyone's here.
原来大家也都过来了啊
We happened to meet there just now.
我们刚才在那边碰巧遇见的
We follow the trace of the Kisei Chuu.
我们沿着规制虫的反应追踪
And then we all met.
然后大家就碰面了
But you seem to have solved it. That's great.
不过你们好像已经解决了 真是太好了
Should it be...
难道说
Is everyone still handling hero activities?
大家也都还在进行英雄活动吗
Why?
怎么了
I thought everyone was the same to Kirara.
以为大家都和云母一样
Unwilling to do it?
当得心不甘情不愿的吗
We will not give up being HXEROS just because of this little thing.
我们不会因为这点小事 就放弃当HXEROS的
Jiji was at a loss at first.
小姬虽然起初很不知所措
But now she seems to understand the fun.
但现在好像也开始理解其中的乐趣了
Please don't use such a misleading expression.
请别用这种容易让人误会的说法啦
Well
话说回来
Unexpectedly, my uncle would be arrested because of the new regulations set by the new governor.
想不到叔叔竟然会因为那个新知事订下的新条例被捕
Eh, too bad human...
这个人类…
What's the matter, Miss Tya Tya?
怎么了吗 茶茶小姐
This human being is always catching my attention.
总觉得这个人类有点让人在意
What do you mean, attention?
妳说让人在意是什么意思
I do not know.
我不知道
But I don't know why I feel this way.
但我不知为何就是有这种感觉
Should it be...
会不会是
Kisei Chuu who mimicked as the governor arrested our uncle.
拟态并成为知事的规制虫将叔叔逮捕
And dissolve HXEROS?
并借此将HXEROS解散呢
What are you saying, Enjo Retto? !
你在说什么啊 烈人
But what I've said is a possibility.
不过确实有这个可能
There's only one way to confirm.
要确认真伪只有一个方法
That is, to meet this guy.
那就是去和这个人见面
SUPER HXEROS
弩级战队HXEROS
Next episode 「Battle! HXEROS」
下一回「决战！HXEROS」